distilnetworks.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Distil Networks

_Last revised on July 25, 2018_

## INTRODUCTION:

Distil Networks, Inc. company that assists businesses (“ _ **Customers**_ ”) to detect and combat automated threats (e.g., content scraping, fraud, brute-force attacks, denial of inventory, etc.) and other information security vulnerabilities (our “ _ **Services**_ ”).

At Distil Networks, Inc., we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy (“ _ **Policy**_ ”) applies to the collection of personal data by Distil Networks, Inc. and Distil Networks Limited (collectively, “ _ **Distil**_ ”, “ _ **we**_ ” or “ _ **us**_ ”). This policy explains our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal data both through our website ([www.distilnetworks.com](https://www.distilnetworks.com/)) and its subdomains (“ _ **Website**_ ”) and in the course of providing our Services.

## 1\. Personal data we collect through the Website

We collect the following types of personal data through our Website:

#### Information you provide us:

In general, you can visit our Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal data about yourself. However, you may provide us with personal data, for example, when you make inquiries about our Services through our “Contact” page or online chat tools, provide us with your contact information for the purpose of sending you white papers, reports, brochures, or to request a demo, attend our events or webinars, or when you sign up to our mailing list. When you communicate with us, we will keep copies of any communications that you send us.  We ask that you not send us, and you do not disclose, any sensitive personal data (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the services or otherwise to us.

#### Information we collect automatically:

We may also collect certain information through our Website by automated means, such as IP addresses, information about your browser, device IDs, your device’s operating system, information about your visit (including the URL clickstream to, through and from our Website), number of Website visits, and other page interactions. We collect this information automatically through the use of various technologies such as cookies and web beacons. For further information about the cookies that we use on our Website and how to exercise your cookie preferences, see the “How we use cookies” section below.

## 2\. How we use personal data collected through the Website

We will only process your personal data in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws. We need certain personal data in order to provide you with access to the Services. If you registered with us, you will have been asked to check a box indicating your agreement to provide this data in order to access our Services or view our content. This consent provides us with the legal basis we require under applicable law to process your data. You maintain the right to withdraw such consent at any time.  If you do not agree to our use of your personal data in line with this policy, please do not use our Website. When fulfilling our contractual obligations to our customers (i.e., the data controllers), we have a legitimate interest in processing certain personal data for such contractual purposes. The information collected through our Website may be used for the following purposes:

  * To provide, operate, optimize and maintain the Website;
  * To deal with inquiries through our Website or to provide you with information and access to resources that you have requested from us;
  * To provide you with offers and information regarding our Services;
  * To analyze the use of our Website for trend monitoring, marketing and advertising purposes;
  * For network security and administration;
  * To investigate and prevent automated threats, other information security vulnerabilities (including unauthorized access to systems or networks), and unlawful activity; and
  * For other legitimate business purposes and other purposes about which we notify you.

In addition to the above, Distil also uses its Services to detect and prevent automated threats and other information security vulnerabilities on its Websites. Please see the section below titled “How we use personal data collected through the Services” for more information regarding how we use any personal data that we may collect through the use of our Services on the Website.

## 3\. Personal data we collect through our Services

When our Customers subscribe to our Services, the following personal data may be collected to help detect automated threats and for other information security purposes (e.g., prevention of content scraping, fraud, brute-force attacks, denial of inventory, etc.).

#### Information collected automatically:

During the course of providing our Services, we assist our Customers in detecting and preventing automated threats and other information security vulnerabilities in relation to our Customers’ digital properties (e.g., websites, mobile applications and APIs). To achieve that end, we analyze the traffic for our Customers’ digital properties and differentiate between the legitimate users of such properties and automated threats. Distil makes these determinations by automated and manual analyses using several potential indicators, such as IP addresses, information about your browser, device identifiers, your device’s operating system, information about your visit (including the URL clickstream to, through and from our Customer’s digital properties), number of visits to a digital property, CAPTCHA challenges and other page interactions, etc. (which we collectively refer to as “Fingerprints”), as well as by configurations set by our Customers. The configurations set by our Customers will depend on the business they operate and the types of automated threats and other information security vulnerabilities that are pertinent to their digital properties. When a Customer subscribes to our Services, our Customers and/or Distil may place Distil cookies on your device and/or run our JavaScript code to enable the collection of Fingerprints. The information is either collected directly from you or collected by our customers and subsequently sent to us. To the extent that any such information constitutes your personal data, we will process such personal data pursuant to this Policy. For information about cookies that are deployed through our Services and how to exercise your cookie preferences, please see the “How we use cookies” section below.

#### Additional information our Customers provide to us:

In addition, our Customers may send additional information to us for the purpose of detecting and preventing automated threats or other information security purposes, including for the purpose of enabling Distil to perform such activities on our Customers’ behalf. For example, they may send us elements of your personal data that you have consented to being shared with us. They might also optionally provide us with information that you share with them through your use their digital properties (e.g., websites, APIs, or mobile applications).

#### Information about our Customers:

If you are a Customer, we may also collect certain personal data about you to enable us to manage our business relationship with you – such as your name, contact details, job title, billing and payment information.

## 4\. How we use personal data collected through the Services

We may use personal data we collect through the Services for the following purposes:

  * To provide the Services to our Customers,
  * To optimize and improve the Services,
  * To analyze the use of the Services for internal business purposes;
  * To provide customer service and support;
  * To send our Customers communications about their account, provide service updates and marketing information;
  * To enable our Customers to share information about automated threats and other information security vulnerabilities;
  * To conduct research and statistical analyses of automated threats and publish related reports;
  * To investigate any unlawful or wrongful activity or unauthorized access to our Services; and
  * For other legitimate business purposes and other purposes about which we will notify you.

## 5\. Information from Social Networking Sites

Our Website include(s) interfaces that allow you to connect with social networking sites (each a “SNS”). If you connect to a SNS through website, you authorize us to access, use and store the information that you agreed the SNS could provide to us based on your settings on that SNS. We will access, use and store that information in accordance with this Policy. You can revoke our access to the information you provide in this way at any time by amending the appropriate settings from within your account settings on the applicable SNS.

## 6\. Personal data we collect from other sources

We may also get information about you from other sources, for example, if you have agreed to share information with one of our partners, suppliers or service providers, we may add this to information we get from our Website or Services.

## 7\. How we share your personal data with third parties

We may share personal data collected through our Website and Services in the following ways:

Information we share with our group companies: We may share your personal data with other members of the Distil group of companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Information we share with our Customers: We may share your personal data collected through the Services with our Customers for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Information we share with our service providers: We may also engage certain trusted third-party service providers, consultants or vendors to assist us in the provision of the Website and Services. We will only share your personal data with such third-parties to the extent necessary to perform such functions and in accordance with the purposes set out in this Policy and applicable laws.

Information disclosed in connection with business transfers: In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, acquisition, dissolution, financing or other similar event, your personal data may be shared or transferred in connection with, or during negotiations of, such event or transaction.

Information disclosed for legal purposes and the protection of others: We may disclose personal data to a third party where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable laws, regulations, legal process or governmental requests. We will also disclose personal data to the extent we believe necessary or appropriate: (i) to respond to claims, judicial orders, subpoenas, warrants or other process issued by a court of competent jurisdiction; (ii) to protect the vital interests of any person; (iii) to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights; and (iii) to stop any activity we consider illegal, unethical or legally actionable, including, without limitation, unauthorized use of digital properties (e.g., websites, APIs, and mobile applications).

## 8\. How we use cookies and similar technologies

“Cookies” are small text files that are placed on your device when you visit (i) our Website or (ii) our Customers’ websites who have integrated Distil’s Services. Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide certain device and other analytical information.

For more information regarding our use of Cookies, please visit our [“Cookies and Similar Technologies” page](https://www.distilnetworks.com/cookie-policy/).

## 9\. Security

We will use appropriate security measures to help protect your personal data. These measures include technical, administrative, physical and organizational measures to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration or destruction. Please be aware that no website is completely secure. Although we will use reasonable endeavors to protect your personal data, you should only access the Website within a secure environment.

## 10\. International transfers

If you are visiting our Website or interacting with our Services from outside the United States (US), including in the European Economic Area, please be aware that your personal data may be transferred to the US and potentially other countries whose data protection laws may not be as protective as those in your country of residence. However, our collection, storage and use of your personal data will at all times be in accordance with this Policy wherever it is processed.  By using the Website and/or the Services, you consent to such transfer, and are representing that you have the right to transfer such information outside your country.  We will take reasonable and appropriate measures to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. For our Services, we will continue to work with our Customers to put in place any appropriate data export solutions that may be needed under applicable laws.  We will only retain your personal data as long as reasonably relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.

## 11\. Your privacy rights

If you are from certain territories (such as the European Economic Area) you may have certain rights in relation to your personal data, such as the right to access, correct, move, amend or delete any personal data we hold about you. If you wish to exercise such rights, or you have any questions or comments concerning your personal data, please contact us at privacy@distilnetworks.com.

If you wish to make a general complaint about our privacy practices, please write to us at the email address above and we will respond within a reasonable time and in accordance with applicable laws.

We will consider and respond to your request promptly and in accordance with any applicable laws.

If you wish to be removed from our mailing list, you can do so my clicking “unsubscribe” in any email communications we send you, or by emailing us at the address above.

## 12\. Participation in EU-US Privacy Shield Framework

Distil Networks, Inc. participates in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework. For more information regarding Distil’s participation in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework, please visit here.

## 13\. Links to other sites

Our Website may contain links to other websites and services. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we are not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information, we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access.

## 14\. Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here and amend the “Last Updated” date at the top of this page. If we make any material changes to the privacy practices relating to our Services, we will amend this privacy policy and notify our Customers more directly – for example by posting a notification or sending a message through their account or by email. We encourage you to review this page frequently to stay informed of the latest modifications.

## 15\. How to contact us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this privacy policy, then please contact us at [privacy@distilnetworks.com](mailto:privacy@distilnetworks.com). If you prefer to mail your complaint, you can contact us at the following address:

Distil Networks, Inc.  
Attn: Data Protection Officer  
4501 N Fairfax Drive, Suite 200  
Arlington, VA 22203  
USA
